

Lê Minh Tuấn 01/10/1999 JAVA FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Introduce

I am a fullstack developer. I have experience working with Java and Javascript along with several other frameworks (Spring, ExpressJS, React, Vue, ...) through several projects. Currently, I want to find a suitable job so that I apply my skills to work. Please contact me using the contact information below.

Contact me

Phone

0326 934 435

Email:

tuanlm110@gmail.com

Linkedin:

@tuanlm110

Address

An Phú, Thuận An, Bình Dương

Knowledge

- Able to self-study and work well under pressure, sociable, easy to integrate with people
- Good understanding of software design, database design, RestfulAPI,
- Good understanding of the Agile and Scrum process
- Deep understanding about OOP, SOLID principles

Education

FPT University HCM 09/2017 - 09/2021

Bachelor Software Engineering

- GPA: 7.5/10
- Excellent student in the 5th Semester
- Partial scholarship during study

Skill

Coding Language

Java, JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Framework

Spring Boot, NodeJS/ExpressJS, VueJS, ReactJS

Database

PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB

Others

Git, CI/CD with Jenkins, AWS Cloud

Pet Project

My Portfolio | Git

- JavaScript, HTML/CSS
- A mini-project to introduce myself and practice basic
- front-end skills

Messenger App | Git

- ExpressJS, VueJS, MongoDB, Firebase, SocketIO, Swagger
- The project is about real-time processing, interface processing through the framework, and communication with the backend through Restful API

MMS | Git

- Spring Boot, PostgreSQL
- This project will connect to the database and business handling the data and return it to the frontend through the Restful API.

DTE Extension | Git

- HTML, CSS, JS
- This chrome extension to export HTML table to CSV file.

Experience

Intern | FPT Software HCM

05/2020 - 09/2020 Java Fullstack Developer

- Designs and creates front-end web for some modules and writes some related API
- Checks feasibility of software prototypes
- Modifies code to fix errors

Capstone 2021 | Mai Vinh Company

03/2021 - 09/2021 Java Fullstack Developer

- Writes API at backend server, config security with handling data at the database.
- Manage CI/CD to the cloud server with the pipeline script.
- Modifies backend code to fix errors